Mother, just once,
can we go to lunch...
제발 한 번만이라도 좋으니까
복장이나 머리, 직장 얘길 않고
식사를 할 순 없는 거냐구요?
...and not talk about what I'm wearing
or where my career is going?
데이트 상대도요
Or who I'm dating.
-Ready for the check?
-God, yes.
계산하시겠습니까?
- 여기요
- 내가 하죠
-I'll take it.
-No, darling.
- 제가 할게요
- 무슨 소리야, 내가 할게
제가 한다니까요
여기요, 가세요
I said I'll take it.
Here, take it. Go. Run.
빨리요
정말 고맙구나
어떻게 갚으려고?
Very sweet.
-And on what they pay you
-Career.
돈 벌잖아요
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm doing fine.
걱정하지 마세요
저 잘하고 있어요
사용이 정지됐군요
I'm afraid this has been denied.
그럴 리가요
That's impossible.
That's all right, dear.
Here you go.
괜찮다
이거 받으세요
The One With The Fake Monica
How'd someone get your card number?
어떻게 남의 신용카드
번호를 알아냈지?
No idea.
Look how much they spent.
나도 몰라
아무튼 엄청나게 써댔어
흥분하지 마, 카드사에선
네가 산 것만 지불하면 된다잖아
You only have to pay
for the stuff you bought.
그건 알지만 무진장 긁어댔어
Still, it's just
such reckless spending.
남의 신용카드를 훔쳐냈으니
닥치는 대로 쓰는 게 당연하지
When somebody steals...
...they've already thrown caution
to the wind.
Wow, what a geek.
They spent $69. 95 on a Wonder Mop.
변태 아냐?
'기적의 걸레'를 69달러에 샀어
That's me.
내가 산 거야
내가 말한 변태는...
You see, when I say geek, I mean
걸레 하나를 70달러에 샀으면
진짜 변태다
The hell with it, you bought
a $70 mop, you're a geek.
저기 봐
Oh, yuck. Ross, he's doing it again.
로스, 쟤 또 저래
마르셀, 그만 좀 비벼라
Marcel, stop humping the lamp.
Stop humping. Now, Marcel, come
Come here, Marcel.
그만해, 마르셀
이리 와, 마르셀!
내 방은 안돼
데려와야겠다
Oh, no. Not in my room.
I'll get him.
아무데나 비비지 못하게
어떻게 좀 해봐
You've got to do something about that.
일시적인 단계일 뿐이야
What? It's just a phase.
조이한테도 항상 그렇게
말하지 않았던가?
Well, that's what we said about Joey.
You'd think you would be
more understanding.
좀 이해해주면 안돼?
그럼 되지만, 그게 안돼
I know. But we're not.
너무 그러지 마
별 일도 아니잖아
Would you all relax?
It's not that big a deal.
마르셀, 그만해
마르셀, 나쁜 원숭이
-Marcel, stop it. Marcel. Bad monkey.
-What?
왜?
내 인형에 어찌나 비벼댔는지
걸레조각이 돼버렸어
Let's say my Curious George
is no longer curious.
모니카, 그걸 또 들여다보고
있는 거야?
You are not still
going over that thing.
이 여자는 내 인생을
살고 있어
-This woman's living my life.
-What?
뭐?
내 인생을 사는데
나보다 훨씬 멋지게 살고 있어
She's living my life,
and she's doing it better than me.
이것 봐
Look at this. Look. She buys tickets
to plays I wanna see.
내가 보고 싶어했던
연극 티켓을 사고
브랜드 이름만 듣고도 쫄았던
가게에서 옷도 사 입고
She shops where
I'm afraid of the salespeople.
300달러에 미술 용품도 샀어
-She spent $300 on art supplies.
-You're not an artist.
넌 화가가 아니잖아
용구만 있으면
됐을지도 모르지
I might be if I had the supplies.
나도 이렇게 살 수 있는데
그렇질 못하잖아
I mean, I could do all this stuff.
Only I don't.
그런 소리 마
너도 근사하게 살잖아
Oh, Monica, come on.
You do cool things.
그래?
한번 비교해볼까?
Really? Let's compare, shall we?
그러긴 너무 늦지 않았니?
Oh, it's so late for "shall we."
내가 공원에서 승마를 하니?
학원에서 강의도 듣고?
Do I horseback ride in the park?
-Do I take classes at the New School?
-No.
아니
너무 불공평해
She's got everything I want,
and she doesn't have my mother.
내가 원하는 걸 다 하면서도
우리 엄마같은 엄마도 없잖아
조이 파포니 어때?
-How about Joey Paponi?
-No, still too ethnic.
그것도 너무 이국적이야
-My agent wants a more neutral name.
-Joey Switzerland?
에이전트가 내 이름이
좀더 중립적이었으면 좋겠대
'조이 스위스'는?
그리고 '조'로 하는 게 좋겠어
Plus, I think it should be Joe.
Joey makes me sound like I'm this big:
조이는 뭐랄까...
이만하다는 느낌이거든
실은 안 그래요
Which I'm not.
조, 조, 조 스탈린?
Joe, Joe, Joe Stalin?
스탈린이라...
Stalin.
스탈린, 내가 아는 이름이야?
많이 들어본 이름인데
Do I know that name?
It sounds familiar.
글쎄, 난 모르겠는데
Well, it does not
ring a bell with me.
연예계 쪽에선 먹혀주는
이름일 거야
But you're more plugged
into that show business thing.
조 스탈린
Joe Stalin.
좋은데
You know, that's pretty good.
조셉으로 하면 어때?
You might wanna try Joseph.
조셉 스탈린
Joseph Stalin.
- 기억하기 쉬울 거야
- 그럼!
-I think you'd remember that.
-Yes.
'버디', 조셉 스탈린 주연
Bye Bye Birdie,
starring Joseph Stalin.
조셉 스탈린 주연의
'지붕 위의 바이올린'
Joseph Stalin is
the Fiddler on the Roof.
안녕
- 안녕
- 어서와
모니카 겔러인데요
Hi. Yes, this is Monica Geller.
제가 선생님 수업을 듣는데
그게 뭐였는지 궁금해서요
I'm taking some classes with you,
and I was wondering what they were.
I've had a recent head injury
and certain numbers
머리 부상을 입은 뒤로
숫자랑 요일이 헷갈려서요
바비큐요?
Barbecue. Oh, did l?
See, there you go.
제가요?
제가 이렇다니까요
뭐하는 거야?
-What are you doing?
-All right, great.
알겠습니다
네, 고마워요
Great. Thanks a lot.
I'm going to tap class.
나 탭 댄스 배울 거야
네 신용카드를 훔친 여자랑
춤을 배우겠다는 거야?
To dance with the woman
that stole your card?
어떻게 생겼는지 보고 싶어
To see what she looks like.
경찰서에 가면
사진이 붙어있을 거야
I'm sure her picture's up
at the post office.
내 인생을 사는 여자야
만나 보고 싶어
I should get to see who she is.
모니카, 정신차려, 그러다 이상한
편집증으로 발전할 수도 있어
You're kind of losing it here.
This is becoming a weird obsession.
이건 광기야, 광기라구
제발 이러지 마, 제발!
This is madness, I tell you.
For the love of God, Monica,
don't do it.
감사합니다
Thank you.
무슨 생각해?
-What do you think?
-Lots of things.
이 생각 저 생각
누가 모니카일까?
-Which one is she?
-May I help you?
무슨 일이죠?
신경쓰지 마세요
저희는 구경하러 왔어요
No, thanks. We're
just here to observe.
그건 안돼요
무용반에서는 무용을 해야죠
You don't observe a dance class.
You dance a dance class.
신발은 저쪽에 있어요
Spare shoes are over there.
무슨 소리야?
What does she mean?
무용을 하란 얘기지
I think she means
"You dance a dance class."
무용반이니까!
일어나, 일어나
-Come on, come on, come on.
-Really?
정말?
저 중에 누가 나인 것 같니?
Do you see anybody
you think could be me?
지난번에 보니까 빈 요구르트
병이 뒹굴고 있던데
Last time there were yogurt
containers lying around after class.
다시는 그런 일 없도록 해요
-Let's not have that happen again.
-She could be you.
저 여자 아냐?
시작합시다
Let's get started.
다섯, 여섯,
다섯, 여섯, 일곱, 여덟
Five, six.
Five, six, seven, eight.
잘 못하겠어
-Okay, I'm not getting this.
-I'm totally getting it.
난 너무 잘하는 거 있지
혼자만 못 따라가는 것 같은
기분 들 때 없니?
Do you ever feel like you're
so uncoordinated?
왜? 똑같이 따라하면 돼
What? You click when they click.
좋아요
모두 파트너를 정해요
All right, everyone grab a partner.
좋아
누가 누가 좋을까
All right. And my dead mother
said you are it. I'm with Rachel.
레이첼이랑 할래
그래
학교 다닐 때 생각난다
Great, it's gym class all over again.
괜찮아요
앞으로 나와서 저랑 해요
You can come up to the front
and dance with me.
옷 홀랑 벗고 악몽을
꾸는 기분이야
Why don't I just take off my clothes
and have a nightmare?
괜찮아요, 저 왔습니다
늦어서 죄송해요
It's okay, it's okay. I'm here,
I'm here. I'm so sorry I'm late.
저 왔어요
Okay, here I am.
So who's the new tense girl?
잔뜩 긴장하신 이 분은
누구죠?
파트너예요
-She's your partner.
-Hi, I'm Monica.
안녕
- 안녕
- 모니카라고 해요
Oh, Monica.
모니카
안녕, 난 모...
Hi, I'm Mon
- 나나예요
- 모나나?
-Nana.
-Monana.
네덜란드인이죠
-It's Dutch.
-You're kidding.
정말요? 저 3년 동안
암스테르담에 있었어요
I spent three years in Amsterdam.
펜실베니아 계예요
Pennsylvania Dutch.
다함께
다섯, 여섯, 일곱, 여덟
And we're dancing.
Five, six, seven, eight.
안녕
Hi.
어서와
-Hey. Where have you been?
-I just got back from the vet.
어디 갔다 왔어?
수의사한테 갔다 오는 길이야
너한테 목에 끼우는 깔때기
하라고 주지 않든?
She's not gonna make you wear
a big plastic cone?
마르셀이 비벼대는 건
일시적인 단계가 아니래
She says Marcel's humping
is not a phase.
성적으로 원숙해진 시기가
와서 그런 거래
Apparently, he's reached
sexual maturity.
너보다 낫다
Hey, he beat you.
앞으로 더 공격적이고
폭력적으로 될 거래
She says, as time goes on,
he's gonna start getting violent.
그럼 어떡해?
So, what does this mean?
더 이상 기를 수 없대
I have to give him up.
말도 안돼
어떻게 그럴 수가 있어?
I can't believe it. This sucks.
이해가 안 가, 태어난 지
얼마나 됐다고 벌써 어른이 됐지?
You just got him.
How could he be an adult already?
그러니까, 어리게만 생각했는데
어느새 나도 모르게
I know. One day he's
this little thing...
그 어린 것이 내 다리에서
떨어지질 않는 거야
...and then he's this little thing
I can't get off my leg.
계속 기를 방법은
없는 거야?
Isn't there any way to keep him?
그래, 수의사 말이...
No. The vet said
unless he's in a place...
원숭이 식으로 사랑을
할 수 있는 곳에서 살지 못하면
...where he has regular access...
...to some monkey loving...
... he's just gonna get vicious.
더 사나워질 거래
동물원에 집어넣어야 돼
I just gotta get him into a zoo.
- 원숭이를 동물원에 집어넣어?
- 나 그거 알아
-How do you get a monkey into a zoo?
-I know.
아니다, 그건 교황을
차에 집어넣는 거였어
No, that's popes into a Vokswagen.
여러 가지 방법이 있어
우선은 주립동물원이 있는데...
We're applying to a lot. Our first
choice would be a big state zoo.
You know, like San Diego. Right?
샌디에고 동물원 말야
하지만 그건 쉽지가 않아
거긴 다른 주니까
But that may just be a pipe dream.
He's out-of-state.
수의사가 마이애미에 사는
사람을 안다고 만나보래
My vet knows someone at Miami,
so that's a possibility.
거긴 해변이잖아
광란의 동물원일 거야
But that's two blocks from the beach.
It's a total party zoo.
안녕
- 어서와
- 안녕
- 우리, 모니카 찾았어
- 뭐?
We found the girl.
경찰에 신고했어?
-Did you call the cops?
-We took her to lunch.
아니, 점심 같이 먹었어
Oh, your own brand
of vigilante justice.
너희 손으로 때려잡으려고?
무슨 소리야?
Are you insane?
This woman stole from you.
그 여자는 네 인생을 훔쳤어
빼앗아갔어, 도둑질을 했다구!
She stole. She's a stealer.
10분만 같이 있어보면
그런 생각 싹 잊혀질 거야
After you're with this woman
for 10 minutes, you forget that.
정말 굉장한 사람이야
얼마나 활기찬 지 몰라!
I mean, she's this astounding person
with this amazing spirit.
그렇겠지, 치어리더한테
훔쳐왔을 테니까
Which she probably stole
from some cheerleader.
모자를 벗긴다!
-Take off their hats.
-Popes in a Vokswagen.
- 차에 교황 집어넣기?
- 응
그거 재밌더라
I love that joke.
설마, 네가 그랬단 말야?
-No way. No way did you do this.
-Monana was very brave.
모나나가 얼마나 용감했는데
정말 굉장했어
We told them we were
the Gundersons in room 61 5...
615호실의 건더슨
가족이라고 했더니
보스턴 셀틱스 팀이
6층을 전세냈다고 하잖아
...only to find out the Boston Celtics
had the entire floor.
우리가 거기 있다는 사실을
알고 난리법석을 떠는 거야
When they saw that we're short
and have breasts....
그래서 우릴 쫓아냈어
내가 호텔에서 쫓겨났다니까!
They threw us out.
I was thrown out of a hotel. Me.
잘한다, 모나나!
Go, Monana.
너희는 꿈속에서만 사는
누구랑은 다르구나
You ladies are not the only ones
living the dream.
난 알지도 못하는 사람들한테
커피 따라주러 가야지
I get to go pour coffee for people
I don't know. Don't wait up.
기다리지 마
우리 내일 브로드웨이 쇼
오디션 보러 가는 거다
Oh, by the way...
...tomorrow we're auditioning
for a Broadway show.
뭐?
-Excuse me?
-There's an open call for Cats.
'캣츠' 오디션이 있어
'메모리즈'를 부르면서
우리 자신을 잊어보는 거야
I'm thinking we sing "Memories"...
...and make complete fools
of ourselves. What do you say?
어때?
아니, 아니
No, no, no. Remember who you're
dealing with here.
네가 날 몰라서 그런데
난 너랑 달라, 사람들 앞에서
탭댄스 추기도 벅차다구
I can't even stand in front
of a tap class.
'암만파' 교도라 그럴 거야
That's because
of your Amish background.
뭐?
펜실베니아 계라면서?
-What?
-You're Pennsylvania Dutch, right?
맞아, 바람만 불어도
간이 오그라드는 성격이야
Right. Till I bought a blow dryer.
Then I was shunned.
나도 전엔 그랬지만 내 인생을
뒤바꿔놓은 영화를 봤지
I was just like you. And then, one day,
I saw a movie that changed my life.
'죽은 시인의 사회' 봤니?
Did you ever see
Dead Poets Society?
응
그 영화가 믿을 수 없을 만큼
지루하더라
I thought that movie was
so incredibly boring.
끝부분에 연극을 못하게 돼서
학생이 자살해 버리잖아
That thing at the end where the kid...
...kills himself
because he can't be in the play?
그때 깨달았지
"꼬마야, 1년만 기다렸다가
독립해서 연극을 하면 되잖아"
It's like, "Kid, wait a year. Leave
home, do some community theater."
난 거길 나오면서 생각했지
I thought, "That's two hours of
my life that I'm never getting back."
"앞으로 내 인생은 지금까지와
완전히 달라지는 거야"
그렇게 생각하니까 겁나는 일이
다 없어지는 거 있지
That scared me more than all
the other crap I was afraid to do.
'미세스 다웃파이어'는
절대 보지 마라
Wow. Then I would definitely
not recommend Mrs. Doubtfire.
맙소사
Oh, God.
스크랜튼에 못 가게 됐어
We didn't get into Scranton.
거긴 안전한 곳이긴 한데
That was, like, our safety zoo.
개나 소만 키운대
They take, like, dogs and cows.
See, I don't know who this
is harder on, me or him.
난 이렇게 힘든데
마르셀은 아무 것도 몰라
이번엔 의자가 당하나봐
I'd say that chair's
taking the brunt of it.
마르셀, 마르셀
안돼!
Marcel. Marcel. Marcel, no.
착하다
Good boy. See?
How can nobody want him?
- 왜 마르셀을 원하지 않지?
- 누군가 나타날 거야
Somebody will.
조셉 스탈린이란 사람이 있대
You know, there already
is a Joseph Stalin.
설마
You're kidding.
사람들을 마구 죽인
러시아 독재자 이름이래
Apparently, he was this Russian
dictator who slaughtered people.
너도 알고 있었을 텐데?
-You'd think you would've known that.
-You'd think I would've.
내가 알고 있었을까?
조이 해덜튼 어때?
Hey, how about Joey Heatherton?
장난하지 마
Come on, I told you
I don't wanna go back to Joey.
'조이'는 안 쓸 거라니까
피비,
예명으로 뭐가 좋을까?
What do you think a good
stage name for me would be?
'화끈한 넘'
Flame Boy.
어디 있는 동물원이죠?
Where exactly is your zoo?
엄밀히 말해 동물원이
아닙니다
Well, it's technically
not a zoo, per se.
상호 교감이 가능한 야생의
경험이라고나 할까요
It's more of an interactive
wildlife experience.
몇 가지만 물어보죠
마르셀이라고 했나요?
Let me ask you some questions
about Marcel.
- 네
- 좋습니다
다른 동물들과 잘 싸우나요?
-Does he fight with other animals?
-No, no. He's very docile.
아뇨, 온순한 편이에요
코너에 몰려도요?
Even if he were cornered?
모르겠는데, 왜요?
Well, I don't know. Why?
작은 물건을 다루는 문제는
어떻죠?
How is he at handling small objects?
바나나를 쥘 수는 있어요
그걸 묻는 거라면요
He can hold a banana,
if that's what you mean.
망치나 칼 같은 건요?
What about a hammer or a small blade?
왜 마르셀이 칼을 들어야
하는데요?
Why would he need a blade?
살쾡이나 뿔달린 동물을
상대하려면 반드시 필요하죠
If he's up against
an animal with horns...
...you got to give him something.
무서운 세상이거든요
Otherwise, it's just cruel.
샌디에고에...
- 샌디에고에 보낼 수 있게 됐어
- 뭐?
-He got into San Diego.
-What?
밖에 나갔다 들어오는데
전화가 울리는 거야, 그래서...
We came back from our walk.
The phone was ringing....
- 받아준대
He's in.
너도 들었니, 마르셀?
샌디에고래, 샌디에고!
Did you hear that, Marcel?
San Diego. San Diego.
큰 실수하시는 겁니다
You're making a mistake.
San Diego's good...
샌디에고도 좋긴 하지만
나한테 넘기면
... but I'll start him off
against a blind rabbit...
눈먼 토끼부터 상대하기로 하고
총액의 20%를 떼어드리죠
...and give you 20% of the gate.
야호!
어디 갔다 오는 거야?
Where have you been?
모니카랑 대사관 파티에
쳐들어갔지
Monica and I just crashed
an embassy party.
대주교한테 뽀뽀도 했어
I think I kissed an archbishop.
주방장이었는지도 모르지
But, of course,
it could've been a chef.
취한 거야?
-Are you drunk?
-No.
아니
거짓말이야, 사실은...
-I'm lying. I am so drunk.
-Oh, God.
엄청 취했어
맙소사
모니카, 전화라도 했어야지
얼마나 걱정했는데
You know what?
You could've called.
I've been worried Monica.
모니카
신난다!
Water rules.
그렇겠지
Yes. Yes, it does.
레스토랑에서 또 전화 왔어
출근할 건지 알고 싶대
The restaurant called. They wanna
know if you're showing up for work.
아니, 서커스에 갈 거거든
Nope. Going to
the Big Apple Circus today.
왜 이러는 거야?
이러다 직장 짤리겠어
You're gonna lose your job.
This is not you.
너답지 않아
아니, 이게 나야
No, it is me.
베개나 두드려 펴고, 고지서
받자마자 돈 내는 사람이 아냐
I'm not just the person
who fluffs the pillows...
...and pays the bills right away.
모니카랑 있으면
난 전혀 다른 사람이 돼
You know, when I'm with her,
I'm so much more than that.
난 모나나라구!
I'm Monana.
여보세요
Hello? Yes, she is.
Hold on a second please.
네, 있어요
잠깐만 기다리세요
모나나, 전화야
Monana, it's for you.
The credit card people.
카드사야
여보세요
Hello.
네
Yes?
이런!
Oh, my God.
감사합니다
-Thanks.
-What?
뭐래?
모니카를 체포했대
They've arrested Monica.
교도소
- 안녕
-Hi.
어때?
How are you?
나쁘진 않아
난 파란색을 좋아하거든
Not too bad.
Fortunately, blue's my color.
나 여기 있는 거
어떻게 알았어?
How did you know I was here?
내가 모니카 겔러야
Because I'm Monica Geller.
네가 쓰고 다닌 거
내 신용카드였어
It was my credit card you were using.
상상도 못했던 일이야
That I was not expecting.
내가 신고한 게
아니란 것만 알아줘
I want you to know,
I didn't turn you in.
고마워
그건 내가 할 말이야
-Thanks.
-No, thank you.
넌 나한테 많은 걸 줬어
You have given me so much.
네가 아니었으면 극장에서
'메모리즈'를 부르지도 못했어
I'd never have gotten to sing...
... "Memories" at
the Winter Garden Theater.
넌 '메모... '만 하다 말았잖아
Actually, you only got
to sing "Memo"
네가 체포되다니...
I can't believe you're here.
What will I do without you?
너 없이 난 뭘 하지?
대사관 파티엔 누가 데려가주고
Who's gonna crash
parties with me?
서커스엔 누가 데려가주니?
Who's gonna take me
to the Big Apple Circus?
모니카, 난 여자들 앞에서
오줌 눠야 할 판인데
I started my day by peeing
in front of 25 other women...
넌 서커스에 누가 데려다주나
그 걱정이나 하고 있니?
...and you're worried about who'll
take you to the circus?
걱정이 아니라 그냥...
궁금해서
Well, not worried,
you know, just wondering.
그렇게 생각할 거 없어
There's nothing to wonder about.
넌 과거의 너로 돌아가는 거야
그게 진짜 네 모습이니까
You'll go back to being who you were.
That's who you are.
- 그럴 필요없어
- 필요 있어
-Not necessarily.
-Yes, necessarily.
그게 뭔지는 모르겠어
암만파 적인 거겠지
I don't know what it is.
Maybe it's the Amish thing.
- 나 사실 암만파 아냐
- 정말? 근데 왜 그런 거야?
-I'm not actually Amish.
-Really? Then why are you like that?
들어올 거예요, 나갈 거예요?
-You, by the door, in or out?
-ln.
들어가요
- 뒤에 계신 분, 다 틀리네요
- 그래도 열심히 하잖아요
-You're getting it all wrong.
-But at least I'm doing it.
샌디에고 행 67기의 탑승객들은
42A로 탑승하시기 바랍니다
This is the final boarding call
for Flight 67...
... to San Diego at gate 42A.
잘 가라, 원숭아
Okay, goodbye, little monkey guy.
All right, I wrote you this poem.
널 위해 시를 적었어
비행기 타기 전에
먹으면 안돼
Okay, but don't eat it
till you get on the plane.
고마워요, 피비 고모
Thank you, Aunt Phoebe.
안녕, 친구
Okay, bye, champ.
샌디에고에 가면 아가씨들이
많겠지만
There'll be a lot
of babes in San Diego...
잘못하면 톡톡히 당한다는
사실 명심해야 한다
... but remember,
there's also a lot to learn.
뭐라고 말해야 할지 모르겠어
원숭이잖아
I don't know what to say, Ross.
It's a monkey.
그냥 지금 기분을 얘기해
Just say what you feel, Joey.
마르셀, 나 배고파
-Marcel, I'm hungry.
-That was good.
잘했어
마르셀, 선물이야
Marcel, this is for you.
비행기 안에서 뭔가 할 일이
있어야 할 것 같아서
It's just, you know, something...
...to do on the plane.
괜찮으면 단 둘이만 있게
해줄래?
If you don't mind,
I'd like a moment alone.
- 그렇게 해
- 그래
-Oh, sure. Absolutely.
-Go ahead.
마르셀, 이리 와
Marcel, come here. Come here.
Come here.
이리 와
우리 꼬마 친구
Well, buddy...
이제 끝이구나
...this is it.
하고 싶은 말이 있어
Just a couple of things
I wanted to say.
보고 싶을 거야
I'm really gonna miss you.
널 잊지 못할 거야
넌 애완동물 이상이었어
You know, I'm never gonna
forget about you.
You've been more than
just a pet to me.
넌 나한테...
You've been more like a
Okay. Marcel.
마르셀, 제발 내 다리 좀
놓을 수 없니?
Would you leave my leg alone?
제발 비벼대지 좀 마
Would you stop humping me
for two seconds?
마르셀... 좋아요
그냥 데려가세요, 어서요
Okay, would you just take him away?
Just take him.
내가 저 손에 낀 장갑이라면
Oh, that I were a glove
upon that hand...
...that I might touch thy cheek.
그대 뺨을
어루만질 수 있을 텐데
좋아요, 수고했어요
-That's fine. Thank you.
-Next.
다음
머쿠쇼 역을 하겠습니다
I'll be reading
for the role of Mercutio.
- 이름이 뭐죠?
- 올드 맥그로인입니다
-Name?
-Holden McGroin.